<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE MyCoReWebPage>
<MyCoReWebPage>

  <section title="Impressum" xml:lang="de" />
  <section title="Imprint" xml:lang="en" />

  <section xml:lang="de">
      <h1>Willkommen bei journals@UrMEL</h1>
      <p class="greeting">Das von der
        <a href="http://www.thulb.uni-jena.de">Thüringer Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Jena</a>
        (ThULB) betriebene Internetportal journals@UrMEL bietet Zugang zu wissenschaftlichen Zeitschriften in digitaler Form.</p>
      <p>Zur Verfügung stehen rund 700 Zeitschriften mit mehr als 230.000 Artikeln und weitere Periodika.
        Diese werden durch die ThULB Jena in Kooperation mit zahlreichen Bibliotheken, Archiven, Verlagen und
        wissenschaftlichen Fachgesellschaften bereitgestellt. Zugänglich sind sowohl retrodigitalisierte historische
        Zeitschriften, als auch Materialien, welche in originär digitaler Gestalt („born digital“) im Rahmen von
        journals@UrMEL publiziert werden. Das Angebot wird ständig erweitert. journals@UrMEL ist Bestandteil der
        <a href="http://www.urmel-dl.de">Universal Multimedia Electronic Library</a>
        (UrMEL).
      </p>
  </section>

  <section xml:lang="en">
      <h1>Welcome to journals@UrMEL!</h1>
      <p class="greeting">The internet portal journals@UrMEL, which is run by the
        <a href="http://www.thulb.uni-jena.de">Thüringer Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Jena</a>
        (ThULB), provides access to scientific journals in digital form.</p>
      <p>There are about 700 journals, containing more than 230.000 articles, and other periodicals available.
        These were provided by the ThULB Jena in cooperation with numerous other libraries, archives, publishers and
        scientific societies. We provide access to retro-digitised historical journals, as well as born-digital materials,
        that were published as part of this project. We are keen to expand our content constantly. journals@UrMEL is a
        part of the
        <a href="http://www.urmel-dl.de">Universal Multimedia Electronic Library</a>
        (UrMEL).
      </p>
  </section>

  <section xml:lang="pl">
    <h1>Witamy na stronie journals@UrMEL!</h1>
    <p class="greeting">Portal internetowy journals@UrMEL, prowadzony przez
      <a href="http://www.thulb.uni-jena.de">Thüringer Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Jena</a>
      (ThULB) oferuje dostęp do cyfrowej kolekcji czasopism naukowych.</p>
    <p>Udostępniamy ok. 700 czasopism, zawierających ponad 230.000 artykułów, oraz inne periodyki które zostały oddane
      do dyspozycji przez ThULB Jena przy współpracy z wieloma bibliotekami, archiwami, wydawnictwami i towarzystwami
      naukowymi. Dostępne są  zarówno zdigitalizowane czasopisma historyczne, jak i materiały pierwotnie elektroniczne
      („born digital”), które zostały opublikowane w ramach projektu journals@UrMEL. Nieustannie staramy się rozszerzyć
      nasz zbiór. journals@UrMEL należy do
      <a href="http://www.urmel-dl.de">Universal Multimedia Electronic Library</a>
      (UrMEL).
    </p>
  </section>

</MyCoReWebPage>